Guide to the Poetry: A Magazine of Verse Records 1895-1961
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Administrative Files, 1912-1936
  - Subseries 2: Major Poets
    - Carl Sandburg, poetry, articles (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - George Santayana, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Wlliam Saroyan, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - George Bernard Shaw, correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Upton Sinclair, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Osbert Sitwell, correspondence, poetry (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - André Spire, correspondence, poetry (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Wallace Stevens, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Wallace Stevens, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Wallace Stevens, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Wallace Stevens, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Wallace Stevens, poetry (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Wallace Stevens, drama (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Genevieve Taggard, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Genevieve Taggard, correspondence, poetry (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Rabindranath Tagore, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Rabindranath Tagore, poetry (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Allen Tate, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Allen Tate, poetry, reviews and articles (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Sara Teasdale, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Sara Teasdale, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Sara Teasdale, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Sara Teasdale, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Sara Teasdale, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Sara Teasdale, poetry, review (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Dylan Thomas, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Eunice Tietjens, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Eunice Tietjens, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Eunice Tietjens, poetry, reviews, articles (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Geraldine Udell, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Louise Untermeyer and Jean Starr Untermeyer, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Louis Untermeyer and Jean Starr Untermeyer, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Louis Untermeyer and Jean Starr Untermeyer, poetry (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Paul Valéry, correspondence SEE ALSO .s Series II, Subseries 1: Juan Ramon Jimenez (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - George Sylvester Viereck, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Harold Vinal, correspondence, poetry (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Ernest Walsh, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Ernest Walsh, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Robert Penn Warren, correspondence, poetry (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Robert Penn Warren, reviews (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Eudora Welty, correspondence (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Glenway Wescott, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Rebecca West, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - John Hall Wheelock, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - John Hall Wheelock, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - John Hall Wheelock, correspondence, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - John Brooks Wheelwright, correspondence, poetry, reviews (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Ella Wheeler Wilcox, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Thornton Wilder, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Marguerite Wilkinson, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Marguerite Wilkinson, correspondence, poetry (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Oscar C. Williams, corresponnce (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - William Carlos Williams, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - William Carlos Williams, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - William Carlos Williams, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - William Carlos Williams, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - William Carlos Williams, poetry, reviews (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Edmund Wilson, correspondence, poetry (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Yvor Winters, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Yvor Winters, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Yvor Winters, poetry, reviews (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Edith Franklyn Wyatt, correspondence, poetry, review (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Elinor Wylie, correspondence, poetry (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - William Butler Yeats, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - William Butler Yeats, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - William Butler Yeats, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - William Butler Yeats, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - William Butler Yeats, poetry (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - William Butler Yeats, miscellaneous SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Marya Zaturenska, correspondence (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Marya Zaturenska, correspondence, poetry, reviews (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Louis Zukofsky, correspondence (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Louis Zukofsky, correspondence, poetry (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Addenda
    - Sub-subseries 1: Biographies
      - Abbe-Andreeva, Abbe, George 1p Aber, Loureine 1p Ackerman, Barbara 1p Adams, Leonie 1p Addison, Medora 1p Adler, Mortimer 1p Adriansen, Rolf 2p Aiken, Conrad 4pp Akins, Zoë 2pp Alden, Ada 1p Aldington, Richard 1p Aldis, Mary 1p Alford, John 1p Allen, Effie 1p Allen, George 1p Allen, Harbor 1p Allen, Hervey 1p Allot, Kenneth 1p Alyea, Dorothy 1p Ames, Lucile 1p Ames, Wesley 1p Anderson, Sherwood 1p Andreeva, Tamara 1p (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Applebaum-Barnard, Applebaum, Sydney 2pp Arkin, David 1p Armstrong, Virginia 1p Arnold, Marguerite 1p Arnstein, Flora J. 1p Arthur, Charlotte 2pp Arvin, Newton 1p Ashley, Winston 1p Askew, Wilson 1p Atkins, Elizabeth 1p Auslander, Joseph 1p Austin, Mary 4pp Bacon, Irving 1p Bailey, Margery 1p Bakeless, John 1p Baker, Karle Wilson 1p Balcom, Nanita 1p Baldwin, Mercy 1p Barber, Mary F. 1p Barber, Solon 1p Bardin, James 1p Barker, Mildred A. 2pp Barnard, Katherine 1p Barnard, Mary 1p (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Barnes-Bishop, Barnes, Florence 2pp Barret, Robert 1p Barret, Mary 1p Barrett, Katherine 1p Barrington, Pauline 1p Barrow, Elfrida 1p Barry, Iris 1p Barton, Mary E. 1p Bassett, Anna F. 1p Beach, Joseph 1p Bealle, Alfred B. 1p Beatty, John C., 1p Beck, John O. 1p Becker, Charlotte 2p Beckwith, Russell 1p Beer, Morris 1p Belitt, Ben 1p Belknap, John 1p Bellamann, H.H. 1p Bendon, Dorothe 2pp Benedict, Libbian 1p Benét, Laura 1p Benét, William Rose 5p Benétt, Anna E. 1p Benson, Stella 2p Beswick, Katherine 1p Betts, Thomas J. 1p Beyers, Meredith 1p Bialk, Elizabeth 2p Biller, Matthew 1p Birnstingl, Phyllis 2p Bishop, John Peale 1p (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Bishop-Boynton, Bishop, Morris 1p Bispham, G. Tucker 1p Bittner, Nelson 1p Black, John 3pp Black, MacKnight 2pp Blackmur, R.P. 1p Blake, Howard 1p Blanding, Henriette de Saussre 1p Blank, Dorothy Ann 1p Blayker, Mary 1p Bliss, Marion L. 1p Block, Ralph 1p Blum, Etta 1p Bodenheim, Maxwell 1p Bogan, Louise 1p Bomberger, Carl 2pp Boner, H. 1p Bonn, John 2pp Bonner, Amy 2pp Boogher, Susan M. 1p Booth, Edward 1p Bostwick, Lawrence 1p Botkin, Benjamin A. 2pp Bottomley, Gordon 1p Boutelle, Grace H. 1p Bowers, Mildred 2pp Bowles, Paul 1p Bowman, Louise M. 3pp Boyle, Kay 2pp Boynton, Luella (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Braganca-Budd, Braganca, Nadejda de 1p Bragin, Moe 1p Brand, Millen 2pp Brégy, Katherine 3pp Bright, Verne 1p Brink, Carol R. 1p Brittain, Robert 2pp Britten, Rollo 1p Britton, J.J. 1p Brodsky, George 1p Brooks, Benjamin 2pp Broomell, Myron 1p Brown, Harry 1p Brown, Marion F. 1p Brown, Mary C. 1p Brown, William C. 1p Brownell, Baker 2pp Brownrigg, Shirley 1p Bruncken, Herbert 1p Bryant, Helen 1p Bryher, Winifred 4pp Brynes, Oscar 1p Bryson, Lyman 1p Buck, Howard 1p Budd, Grace (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Bunting-Carmer, Bunting, Basil 1p Burgess, Robert 1p Burlin, Natalie 1p Burns, Colette 1p Burnshaw, Stanley 2p Burrows, Edwin 1p Burton, Richard 1p Buss, Kate 1p Butler, Jessie S. 2pp Butts, Dorothy 1p Buzzell, Francis 2pp Cades, Hazel 4pp Caie, Harriet 2pp Cairns, Dolores 1p Calahan, Ellwood 1p Caldwell, Doris 1p Call, Oliver 1p Campbell, Doris 1p Campbell, Floy 1p Campbell, Isabel 2pp Campbell, Joseph 2pp Campbell, Kathleen 1p Canby, Marion 1p Canfield, Mary C. 1p Cannell, Skipwith 1p (includes note from Ezra Pound) Cantor, Eli 1p Carden, Guy 1p Cardozo, Nancy 1p Carmer, Carl 3pp (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Carnevali-Clark, Carnevali, Emanuel 3p Carrall, Godwin 1p Carruth, Hayden 1p Carry, Mabel 1p Carter, David 1p Carter, Louise 1p Carus, Helena 1p Catel, Jean 3pp Caughey, M.L. 1p Cavin, Miriam 1p Chadwick, J.C. 1p Channing, Anne 1p Chapin, Helen 1p Chapin, Katherine 2pp Charles, Mary (Susan Shrine) 1p Chase, Marion M. 1p Chattopadhyaya, H. 1p Chen, Kwei 1p Cheyne, Elizabeth 2pp Chip, Elinor 1p Chown, Harold 1p Christoph, Charles de Guire 2pp Christopherson, Merrill 1p Chubb, Thomas 1p Churh, Peggy 2pp Church, Richard 1p Citkowitz, Israel 1p Clark, Addison 3pp Clark, Eunice 1p Clark, Hazel 1p (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Coates-Crow, Coates, Archie A. 2pp Coates, Grace S. 2pp Coatsworth, Elizabeth 1p Coblentz, Catherine 1p Cochran, Dorothy C. 1p Code, Grant 1p Coffin, Robert 1p Coleman, Ruth 1p Comstock, Mary E. 1p Conant, Isabel F. 1p Conklin, Groff 1p Conkling, Grace Hazard 2pp Conrad, Sherman 1p Cook, Harold 1p Cooke, Edmund V. 2pp Cooksley, S. Bert 1p Cooley, Julia 1p Cooper, Doris 1p Corbett, Charlotte 1p Cornelius, Helen 2pp Corning, Howard 1p Cory, Daniel M. 2pp Cournos, John 1p Cowell, Harry 2pp Cowley, Malcolm 4pp Cox, Eleanor 2pp Cozzens, Evangeline 1p Crawford, John 1p Crawford, Nelson 1p Creekmore, Hubert 1p Cresson, Abigail 1p Crew, Helen C. 1p Croft-Cooke, Rupert 1p Cromwell, Gladys 1p Crook, Kile 1p Cross, Leslie 3pp Crow, Florence 3pp Crow Martha Foote 1p (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Cullen-Deacon, Cullen, Countee 1p Cummins, Cornelia 2pp Cunningham, C. 1p Cunningham, J.V 1p Cunningham, Nora 1p Curran, Edwin 1p Curtis, Christine 1p Cushing, Edward 1p Cuthbert, Clifton 1p Dahlberg, Edward 1p Dall, Ian 1p Dalton, Power 2pp Daly, James 1p Dalziel, Kathleen 3pp Damon, S. Foster 1p Daniels, Earl 1p Dargan, Edwin 1p Dargan, Olive 1p Davenport, Russell 1p Davidman, Joy 2pp Davis, Ethel 1p Davis, Fannie Stearns 2pp Davis, H.L. 1p Davis, Leland 1p Davison, Edward 2pp Dawson, Grace S. 1p Day Lewis, C. 1p Deacon, Anne 1p (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - De Acosta-Dolson, De Acosta, Merceds 1p De Bullet, Gene 1p De Ford, Miriam 1p De Garis, Charles SEE C. Frandegaris De Gourmont, Remy 3pp Dejong, David 1p De La Selva, Salomon 1p De Montalk, Count Geoffrey 5pp De Nair 1p Denby, Edwin 2p Denney, Reuel 2pp Deschere, Carol 1p Deutsch, Babette 1p Diller, Mary 2pp Dine, Reitza 1p Dismorr, Blanche 1p Dixon, Deakin 1p Dodd, Lee Wilson 3pp Dogge, Alzire SEE Nelson, Alzire Dodge, Anne A. 1p Dolson, Eugene 3pp (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Donaldson-Dyment, Donaldson, Zoe 2pp H.D. (Hilda Doolittle) 1p Dorset, Edmund 1p Dos Passos, John 1p Doughty, Isabel 1p Doughty, Leonard 1p Douglas, Mona 1p Dow, Dorothy 1p Dowd, F. Harrison 9pp Doyle, Arthur 1p Doyle, Camilla 1p Doyle, Marion 1p Dransfield, Jane 1p Dravo, Margaret D. 1p Dresbach, Glenn Ward 2pp Dreyspring, Mary (pen name, Margaret Dreyer) 1p Drinkwater, John 1p Driscoll, Louise 1p Duerr, Edwin 1p Duff, James L. 1p Duff, Naomi 2pp Dumont, Henry 1p Duncan, Thomas 1p Dunning, Rlaph C. 1p Durham, Elizbeth 1p Durling, Dwight 2pp Durst, Doris 1p Dutton, Margan 1p Du Von, Jay 1p Dwyer, Mary 1p Dykstra, Leslie 1p Dyment, Clifford 1p (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Earnshaw-Fitts, Earnshaw, Ruth 1p Eberhart, R.G. 1p Eberstein, Myrtle 1p Edgerton, Gladys 1p Edsall, Florence S. Small 2pp Eiseley, Loren 1p Elliston, George 2pp Ellyson, John R. 1p Elmendorf, Mary 1p Emerson, Dorothy 1p Emery, Jane 1p Emory, William 1p Endicoff, Max 1p Engle, Paul 1p Enslow, Mary Constance 1p Erwin, Margaret 1p Esler, Richard 1p Estavan, Lawerence 1p Evans, Abbie H. 1p Evans, Bronwen 1p Everson, Ronald 1p Everson, William 1p Fairburn, A.R.D. 1p Fawcett, Kixie McCarty 1p Fearing, Kenneth 1p Fendell, Solomon 1p Fenton, Carroll 1p Fenworth, Rebekah 1p Ferguson, Virginia M. 1p Ferril, Thomas 1p Fiske, Arthur Davidson 1p Field, Anne 1p Field, Sara Bard 1p Finerty, John 1p Fink, Robert 1p Finnegan, Alice W. 1p Fisher, Mahlon 1p Fitts, Dudley 1p (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Fitzell-Fuller, Fitzell, Lincoln 1p Fitzgerald, Edward 1p Fitzgerald, William 1p Flagg, Sue S. 1p Flanner, Hildegarde 1p Fletcher, John Gould 3pp Flexner, Hortense 1p Flint, F.S. 1p Flowers, Nancy 1p Flynn, Jan 1p Folsom, Franklin 1p Foulke, Mildred 1p Fox, Moireen 3pp Francis, Helen 2pp Frandegaris, C. 1p Frank, Florence 1p Frantz, Laurent 1p Fraser, Margaret 1p Fraser, Marjorie Frost 1p Frederick, John 1p Freedman, B.M. 1p Freeman, Joseph 1p Freeman, Mason A., Jr. 2pp Freeman, Tom 1p Friedlaender, V.H. 1p Friedrich, Rlaph 1p Friend, Robert 1p Frieseke, Frances 1p Frost, Elizabeth H. 1p Frost, Evelyn G. 1p Frost, Frances M. 1p Fryer, Cecily 1p Fuller, Ethell Roming 3pp Fuller, Rex 1p (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Gaines-Goldsmisth, Gaines, Ruth 1p Galahad, Joseph 1p Garland, Marie 1p Garnett, Louise 1p Garrett, George 2pp Garvin, Katharine 1p Gedder, Virgil 1p Gemmell, Jean 1p Gerry, W.H. 1p Gessler, Clifford 2p Gibran, Kahlil 1p Gidlow, Elsie 3pp Gilbert, Anne 1p Gilbert, Elizabeth 2pp Gilbert, Geo 1p Gilbert, Helen 1p Gilbert, Rudolph 2pp Gilchrist, Marie 1p Gildart, Robert 1p Gill, Frances 2pp Gill, John 2pp Gillespie, John 1p Gillette, Charles 1p Gillian, Strickland 2pp Gillialand, Winona 1p Ginsberg, Doris 1p Glaentzer, Helen 1p Glaenzer, Richard 1p Glascock, K. Irene 1p Gleason, George 1p Gleason, Harold 1p Glines, Ellen 1p Glover, Guy 1p Goetz, Philip 1p Golding, Louis 2pp Goldsmith, Beatrice 3pp (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Goldring-Grudsky, Goldring, Douglas 3pp Gonzales, N.V.M. 1p Gonzales, A.R. (pseudonym of Dorothy Hipp) 2pp Goodell, Elbra 1p Gordon, Don 1p Gordon, Frank 4pp Gorman, Herbert 1p Gower, M.G. 1p Graham, Stephen 1p Granich, Irwin 1p Grannis, Anita 1p Graves, Alfred P. 1p Graves, Harley 1p Graves, Robert 1p Greene, Rlaph 1p Greenhood, David 1p Greenlee, John 1p Greenwood, Julia W. 2pp Gregory, Allene 1p Grier, Mary 1p Griffn, Elizabeth 1p Griffin, William 1p Gruber, Ruth 4pp Grudin, Louis 1p Grudsky, Leo 1p (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Hagedorn-Hays, Hagedorn, Hermann 1p Haley, Laura 1p Hall, Amanda 1p Hall, Hazel 1p Hall, Josef W. (pseudonym of Upton Close) 1p Hamilton, A. Gordon 1p Hamilton, David 2pp Hamilton, Flora 1p Hamilton, Virginia 1p Hammond, Eleanor 2pp Hanes, Leigh 2pp Harding, Ruth 1p Hardy, Thomas 1p Harrington, Katharine 1p Harris, Sydney 1p Harrison, Geneva 1p Hart, Louise 1p Hart, Richard 1p Hartmus, Laurence 1p Hartsock, Ernest 2pp Harvey, Shirley 1p Harwood, Ruth 1p Haste, Gwendolen 2pp Hauser, Jacob 2pp Hawkins, Dorothy 1p Hawkridge, Emma 1p Hayakawa, S. Ichiye 1p Hayes, Raphael 1p Hays, Hoffman 1p (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Healy-Hitchcock, Healy, John 2pp Hedges, Ada 1p Hemenway, Isabel 1p Henderson, Daniel 1p Henderson, Rose 1p Henderson, Ruth 1p Henning, Marlys 1p Henrici, Anthony 1p Hensel, Gladys 2pp Henson, Richard 1p Heppenstall, Rayner 2pp Herald, Leon S. 1p Herter, Suzette 1p Hesse, Hermann 1p Heyward, DuBose 2pp Hickey, Florence 1p Hicky, Daniel 1p Hickler, Rosalie 1p Hieronymus, R.E. 1p Hill, Creighton 1p Hill, Dana 1p Hill, Marvin Luther (Mrs.) 1p Hillman, Carolyn 1p Hillyer, Robert 3pp Hinton, Leonard 1p Hipp, Dorothy, SEE Gonzales, A.R. Hitchcock, Henry 1p (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Hoffman-Hyatt, Hoffman, George 2pp Hoffman, Julius 1p Hogrefe, Pearl 1p Holberg, Ruth 1p Holden, Raymond 1p Holland, Isabel 2pp Holley, Horace 1p Holloway, Roberta 3pp Hollowell, Grace Baer 1p Holme, Jamie S. 2pp Holmes, John 3pp Holoubek, Mary 1p Hope, Welborn 1p Hopkins, Ruth 1p Horgan, Paul 1p Hosken, Raymond 2pp House, Roy Temple 1p Houston, Margaret 1p Houston, Peyton 1p Howard, J.Z. 1p Howell, Elizabeth 1p Hubbell, Lindley 1p Huckfield, Leyland 2pp Huddleston, Mabel 2pp Hughes, Langston 1p Hughes, Richard 2pp Hughes, Robert 2pp Huntington, Julia 1p Hutchinson, Velma 1p Hutchinson, Hazel C. 2pp Huxley, Julian 1p Hyatt, Jack Jr. 1p (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Idle-Judson, Idle, E. Doreen 1p Iglehart, emily P. 1p Imbs, Bravig 1p Jackson, Jessie 1p Jackson, Phylilis 1p Jacobsen, Josephine 1p James, Seth 1p Jenkins, Oliver 1p Jenks, Tudor 3pp Jennings, Frances 1p Jennings, Leslie N. 2pp Jesson, Frederick 1p Johnson, A.E. 1p Johnson, Arthur 1p Johnson, Edward 1p Johnson, Fenton 1p Johnson, Geoffrey 1p Johnson, Ida 1p Johnson, Josephine 4pp Johnson, Maurice 1p Johnson, Roy 1p Johnson, Siddie 1p Johnson, W. 1p Jones, Leila 1p Jones, Louisa B. 3pp Jones, Mary H. 3pp Judson, Margaret 1p (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Kagawa-Kwan, Kagawa, Gunici 1p Kahn, Marcella 1p Kaplan, Miriam 1p Kapp, David 1p Kapstein, Israel 1p Karageorgevitch, Dorothy 1p Katz, Naomi 1p Keller, Martha 1p Kelley, Edith 1p Kellogg, Charlotte 1p Kelly, Grace V. 2pp Kelly, Leone 1p Kennedy, Celia 1p Kennedy, Leo 1p Kent, Arthur 2pp Kerigan, Anthony 1p Keysner, Blance 1p Kidd, Walter (pseudonym, Conrad Pendleton) 1p Kilmer, Aline 1p Kimmell, Stanley 1p Kinsolving, Sally B. 1p Kirkpatrick, Doris 1p Kizer, [Mabel] Ashley 2pp Klein, Abraham 1p Klein, Edith 1p Knapp, Marjorie 1p Knevels, M.E. 1p Knight, Lulu W. 1p Knister, Raymond 1p Koenig, Eleanor C. 1p Kohn, walter 1p Kortrecht, Augusta 1p Kresensky, Raymond 1p Kreymborg, Alfred 1p Kueffner, Louise M. 1p Kunitz, Stanley J. Kwan, Moon 4pp (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - Laedline-Lewis, Laedline, Laura L. 1p Laing, A.K. 1p Lamar, Frances K. 1p Lanyon, Carla 1p Lapin, Adam 1p Larkins, Margaret 1p Larsson, R. Ellsworth 2pp Lattimore, Richmond 2pp Lawrence, Gordon 1p Lawrence, Harriet 1p Lawrence, Rebecca P. 1p Leader, Pauline 1p Lear, David 1p Lechliner, Ruth 2pp Le Clercq, Jacques [Paul Tanaquil, pseudonym] Le Cron, Helen C. 1p Lee, Agnes 1p Lee, Borghild 2pp Lee, Muna 3pp Leekley, Richard 1p Lehmer, Derrick 1p Le Noir, Phil 2pp Leonard, Dorothy 1p Leonard, William E. 4pp Lesemann, Maurice 1p Lewis, Arthur 2pp Lewis, Emily 2pp Lewis, Kenneth R. 2pp Lewis, May 1p (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Lind-MacMullen, Lind, Robert 2pp Link, Seymour 2pp Lippmann, Alice d. 1p Lister, Queene B. 1p Litsey, Edwin 1p Litsey, Sarah 1p Littledale, Mary 1p Livesay, Florence R. Lockett, Rowena 2pp Long, Harriet 1p Lorca, Federico Garcia 1p Lorimer, Emilia 2pp Lounberg, Katherine 1p Loving, Pierre 1p Lowe, Robert Liddell 1p Lowenfels, Walter 4pp Luckhardt, Hertha 1p Luhan, Mabel D. 1p Lyman, Dean B., Jr. 1p Lynch, Genevieve 1p Maas, Willard 1p MacCaughey, Vaughan 1p MacDonald, Jessie 1p MacIntyre, Carlyle 1p Mackereth, James 1p Mackay, Margaret 1p Mackery, Marjorie 1p MacLean, Katharine 1p MacLeish, Archibald 1p Macleod, Joseph 2pp MacLeod Norman 1p MacMullen, Lilian M. 1p (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Maddow-May, Maddow, Ben 1p Magaret, Helene 1p Malam, Charles 1p Mallatt, Lola 1p Mangan, Sherry 1p Manning, Frederic 1p Manning-Sanders, Ruth 1p Manuel, C.H. 1p Marco, Angela (pseudonym of Annie Mearkle) 2pp Maring, Helen 1p Marini, Myra 1p Maris, [Sister] Stella SEE Stella, (Sister) Maris Markham, Lula 2pp Marks, Margaret 1p Markun, Leo 1p Marlatt, Earl 1p Marshall, Lenore 2pp Martin, James 1p Mason, Francis C. 1p Mason, F. W. 2pp Masseck, Clinton 1p Mastin, Florence R. 2pp Matheson, Mary 1p Matson, Mabel 1p Mavrogordato, John 1p Maxwell, Gilbert 1p May, Henry 1p (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - McAlmon-Meyer, McAlmon, Robert 2pp McCall, Virginia A. 2pp McCarthy, J. Russell 2pp McClellan, Walter 1p McClure, John 1p McCord, David 1p McCormick, Virginia 1p McCourt, Edna W. 1p McCoy, Samuel 1p McCreary, F.R. 2pp McCreary, W.H. 1p McFadden, Athena 1p McGiffert, Gertrude H. 1p McGurrin, Buckley 1p McKenny, Margaret 1p McKenzie, Roderick 1p McKinney, Isabel 1p McLemore, Dorothy 1p McLeod, LeRoy 1p McPeek, James 1p McVickar, Dorothy 1p Meeker, Marjorie 1p Melendez, Engracia 1p Merryman, Mildred P. 1p Merten, Jack 1p Meuttman, Margaret 1p Meyer, Emma V. 1p (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Micelson-Moodey, Michelson, Max 1p Middleton, Scudder 1p Migel, Parmenia 1p Milam, May Thomas 1p Miles, Josephine 2pp Millay, Kathleen 2pp Miller, Fred R. 1p Miller, J. Corson 1p Miller, Mary W. 1p Miller, Martha 2pp Milligan, Clarence 2pp Millspaugh, Clarence 1p Miniter, Edith 2p Mirick, Edith 1p Mitalsky, Frank 1p Mitchell, Ruth C. 2pp Mitchell, Susanna 1p Mixter, Florence 1p Mondaca, Carlos 1p Montgomery, Lois 2pp Moodey, John S. 1p (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Moore-Newton, Moore, Agnes 2pp Moore, Barbara 1p Moore, Catherine 1p Moore, Marianne 1p Moore, Virginia 2pp Morgan, Edwin 2pp Morgan, Emanuel (pseudonym of Witter Bynner) 2pp Morrell, Edith 1p Morrill, Jane 1p Morrison, Frances 1p Morrissette, Pat 1p Morse, Katherine D. 3pp Moses, William R. 2pp Muckley, Helen 1p Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1p Muňoz Marin, Luis 1p Murphy, C.R. 1p Murphy, Richard A. 1p Murray, Ada F. 2pp Musser, Benjamin 1p Needham, Wilbur 1p Nelson, Alzire 1p Nethercot, Arthur 1p Neville, Helen 1p Newman, Israel 1p Newman, Stanley 1p Newton, Katherine 1p Newton, Mary 1p (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Nicholl-Olson, Nicholl, Louise T. 2pp Niedecker, Lorine 1p Nienaber, Allison 1p Noguchi, Yone 2pp Nolte, Julius 1p Norden, Peter 1p North, Jessica Nelson 2pp Norton, Grace Fallow 2pp Novák, sonia R. 1p Noyes, Alfred 3pp Nutt, Howard 1p Oaks, Gladys 1p O’Bolger, J.D 1p O’Brien, Edward 2pp O’Brien, Jean 2pp O’Byrne, Cathal 2pp O’Donnell, Charles L. (Father) 1p O’Donnell, George M. 1p Oleson, Helmer 1p Oliver, Wade 2pp Olsen, Charles 1p Olson, Ted 1p (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - O’Malley-Pillin, O’Malley, Ernie 1p Opdycke, Mary E. 1p Oppenheim, James J. 1p Orean, Thomas 1p Orr, Patrick (pseudonym of Margaret Adelaide Wilson) 1p Ostenso, Martha 2pp Owen, Louise 1p Page, Florence 1p Pangborn, H.L. 1p Paquette, Donald 2pp Paradise, Viola 1p Parker, Phillip 1p Partridge, Pauline 1p Payne, Anne B. 1p Pearce, Anne B. 1p Pearce, Helen 1p Pease, Josephine 1p Pennell, J. Stanley 1p Pergament, Lola 1p Peterkin, Julia M. 1p Peterson, Anne Deacon (SEE Deacon, Anne) Peterson, Edwin 1p Petgen, Dorothy 1p Petrunkevitch, Wanda 1p Peyton, John 1p Pfund, Helen 1p Phelps, Arthur, 1p Phipps, Betty 1p Pickerill, Edward 2pp Pierson, Ruth B. 2pp Pillin, William 1p (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Pinckney-Purnell, Pinckney, Josephine 1p Piper, Edwin F. 1p Pitter, Ruth 2pp Pollitt, Josephine 1p Porter, Kenneth W. 2pp Post, Mary B. 2pp Pound, Ezra (written by Homer L. Pound) 1p Powers, Jessica 1p Pressley, Janet 3pp Preston, John H. 1p Preuss, Wolfgang 1p Priest, George W. 2pp Probst, Leetha J. 2pp Probstfield, Edris M. 1p Prokosch, Frederic 1p Provines, Eloise E. 1p Pudney, John 1p Pulse, Helene 1p Purnell, Idella 4pp (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Quinn-Riding, Quinn, John R. 3pp Rago, Henry 1p Rakosi, Carl (pseudonym of Callman Rawley) 1p Ramsay, Janet 2pp Rand, Robert 1p Ratcliffe, Dorothy Una 1p Ravenel, Beatrice W. 1p Read, Robert 1p Reavey, George 1p Redfield, Robert, J. 1p Reed, John 1p Rees, Arthur D. 3pp Reeve, Paul 1p Reid, Dorothy E. 1p Reid, Phyllis 2pp Reinstein, Herman 1p Renaud, Floria 1p Replansky, Naomi 1p Reynolds, Julia 1p Reznikoff, Charles 1p Rice, Ruth 1p Rich, Daniel 1p Richards, Dora 1p Richardson, Mabel Kingsley 3pp Richter, Fritz (Mrs. Nat Einhorn) 1p Ridge, Lola 1p Riding, Laura 4pp (Box 44, Folder 10)